A Guide to the Records of Lieutenant Governor Lawrence Doulgas Wilder, 1975-1990 (bulk 1986-1989)
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and Subject Files [Accession 35539], 1975-1990 (bulk 1986-1989)., Extent: 8.15 cu. ft. (19 boxes). (Box 1-19)
  - Subject and reference files
    - Local government Antitrust protection, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Messages, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - New bond stories and articles, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Newport News City Council race, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Political technology, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Railroad assessment, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Signs and portable billboards, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Southern Legislative Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Spousal abuse, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Upcoming newsletter, 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Uranium issues, 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Uranium issues, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    - Uranium issues, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Uranium issues, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Uranium prospecting, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Urban Enterprise Act of Kemp-Garcia, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
    - Virginia Compensation Board, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Weather Service, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Water pipeline, Corps of Engineers, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Whittaker Hospital (Newport News, Va.), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Files [Accession 33696], 1982-1989., Extent: 18.9 cu. ft. (54 boxes). (Box 20-73)
  This series consists of correspondence and subject files, 1982-1989, of Lieutenant Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder. The series is housed in fifty-four (54) boxes and include agendas, clippings, correspondence, memorandum, minutes, newsletters, notes, press releases, publications, reports, schedules, and speeches, among other materials. The collection is further divided into sections: Administration; Commissions; Issues, Schools; and Subject and reference files.
  The Administration records consists of correspondence with Agency heads and Secretaries, appointments and recommendations to boards and commissions, audit and financial reports, annual reports of departments, press releases, invitations to seminars and conferences held at agencies, official election results compiled reports, meeting announcements, and correspondence from constituents regarding various issues.
  The Commission records consists of agendas, clippings, memorandum, minutes, and reports (drafts and final) of several commissions including: Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government, Governor's Commission on Federal Funding of State Domestic Programs, Governor's Community Crime Prevention, Governor's Conference on Infant Mortality, Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, and the Virginia Military Advisory Commission, among others.
  The Issues records consist of brochures, clippings, and correspondence from constituents regarding a variety of issues. Topics include AIDS, landfills, tolls on bridges, cuts to special education, sex education in school, flag burning, safety of four wheelers, health care, lottery, non prescription drug taxes, parental consent bill for abortions, seat belts, transportation, and other topics.
  The Schools records consist of invitations to Lt. Governor Wilder to attend reunions and graduations and invitations to speak at schools.
  The Subject and reference file records are arranged alphabetically by topic or by last name of the person contacting the Lt. Governor. Included are correspondence with other state Lt. Governor's; annual report of the Chesapeake Bay Commission; minutes and reports from the Black History Museum and Culture Center; correspondence with Congressmen and Delegates; report from the Joint Subcommittee Studying Election Laws; brochures from companies; trips to Israel and Japan; letters from constituents requesting help with issues or inviting the Lt. Governor to celebrations; invitation to attend the Association of Minority Enterprises of New York awards dinner; minutes from the Jobs for Virginia Graduates, Inc.; annual reports of the Joint Center for Political Studies; and letters from school students requesting biographical information and photographs of Lt. Governor Wilder for school projects, among other topics.
  - Administration
    - Administration, Sec. of, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Agency Heads, List of, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Aging, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Appointments, Boards and Commissions, Baliles Administration, 1986 January-June (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Appointments, Boards and Commissions, Baliles Administration, 1986 January-1987 September (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Appointments, Boards and Commissions, Baliles Administration, 1986 January-1987 September (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Appointments, Boards and Commissions, Baliles Administration, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Appointments, Boards and Commissions, Baliles Administration, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Attorney General, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Aviation, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Budget Bill, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Commerce, Sec. of, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Commonwealth, Sec. of, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth, Sec. of, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Comptroller, Office, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Comptroller, Office, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Comptroller, Office, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
    - Commerce, Dept., 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Community Colleges, State Board, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Community College System, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Conservation and Historic Resources, Dept. of, 10986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Corrections, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Corrections, State Board, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Council of Higher Education, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Courts, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Credit Union, State, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Dentistry, Board of, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Elections, State Board of, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Elections, State Board of, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Executive Orders, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Fellows, Governor, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Finance, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Finance, Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Gov. Baliles, Correspondence with, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Health, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Human Resources, Sec. of, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Lottery, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mines, Minerals, and Energy, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Organization chart, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Police, State, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Press releases, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Social Services, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1983-1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - State Fair of Virginia, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Surplus Property, State, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Tax Reform Plan, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Taxation, Dept. of, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Tourism, Division of, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, General, 1987-1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, Report, Affirmative Action Plan, 1987-1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, Reports, Allocation of Funds, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, Allocation of Funds, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, Reports, Raising the speed limit, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, Reports, Misc., 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Treasury, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Valentine Museum, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Liaison Office, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Commissions
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Inaugural meeting, 1987 November 4 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Meetings, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Report, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Report, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Report, Drafts, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Report and photograph, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, U.S. Dept. of Justice, Articles, 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Commission on the Future of Virginia's Judicial System, Video, ca. 1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Local Government, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Commission on Federal Funding of State Domestic Programs, Community Action Assessment Study, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Commission on Federal Funding of State Domestic Programs, Community Development Committee Report, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Commission on Federal Funding of State Domestic Programs, Environmental Committee Report, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Commission on Federal Funding of State Domestic Programs, Windfall Tax Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Community Crime Prevention Awards Program, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Community Crime Prevention Awards Program, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Conference on Infant Mortality, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, Meetings, 1986 December (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, Meetings, 1987 April (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, Meetings, 1988 April (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
    - Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, Meetings, 1989 July (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Education Block Grant Advisory Committee, Reports, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Commission, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Commission on, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Commission on the Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Establishment of, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Meeting binder, 1986 October 22 (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Meeting binder, 1987 April 27 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Meeting binder, 1987 December 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Meeting binder, 1988 May 23 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Meeting binder, 1989 May 30 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Legal Affairs Committee report, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Washington Dulles Task Force, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Issues
    - AIDS, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Asbestos, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Brown-Ferris Industries Landfill (Cumberland Co., Va.), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Clean Air Act, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Coleman's Bridge, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Education, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Education, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Falwell Tax exemption, 1983-1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Family Life Education, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Flag burning, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Four wheelers, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Health care, 1985-1989 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Homeless in Virginia, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - House Bill 539, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Impact and transfer taxes, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Issues, General, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Issues, General, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Issues, General, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
    - Issues, General, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - Issues, Lake Gaston Pipeline, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Lottery, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - The Making of Virginia's Laws, Remarks, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Manassas (Va.) Battlefield, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Medical malpractice insurance, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Mental health, 1987-1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Non-prescription drug taxes, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Optometrists, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Parental Consent Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Parental Consent Bill, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Parental Consent Bill, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - Route 288, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Seat belts, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Tax relief, 1986-1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Veterans cemetery, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Schools
    - Armstrong High School (Richmond, Va.), 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Appalachian Learning Center, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Averette College, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Beaumont Learning Center (Beaumont, Va.), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - California State University, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Chesterfield County Public Schools, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Davidson College, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School (Norfolk, Va.), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Ferrum College (Rocky Mount, Va.), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - George Mason University, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Hanover County Public Schools, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Hampton University, 1986-1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Harvard University, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Henrico County Public Schools, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Howard University, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - James Madison University, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Longwood College, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Mary Washington College, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Medical College of Virginia, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 January-March (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 April (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 May (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 June-July (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 August-December (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 January-March (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 April-November (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Publications, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk Public Schools, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk State University, 1985-1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Northern Virginia Community College, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Old Dominion University, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Petersburg Public Schools, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Piedmont Community College, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Princeton University, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Radford University, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Richmond Public Schools, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - University of Virginia, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - University of Virginia, 1987-1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Cooperative Extension Service, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute, 1986-0987 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Virginia State University, 1985-1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Virginia State University, 1987-1989 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Tech, 1985-1988 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - William and Mary College, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Subject files
    - A, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - A, 1987 January-May (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - A, 1987 June-December (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - A, 1988 January-August (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - A, 1988 September-December (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - A, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Africare, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - AIDS, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - America, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO, 1985-1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - American Industrial Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - American Newspaper Publishers Association (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - American Red Cross, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Arkansas, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Arts Council, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Association of Minority Enterprises of NY, Inc., 1987 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Arizona, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - B, 1985 December-1986 March (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - B, 1986 April-July (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - B, 1986 August-September (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - B, 1986 October-December (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - B, 1987 January-May (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - B, 1987 June-December (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - B, 1988 January-June (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - B, 1988 July-December (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - B, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Bar Association (Richmond, Va.), 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - BDM International, Inc., 1989 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Big Brothers, Big Sisters, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Biography-Photo requests, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
    - Biography-Photo requests, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Biography-Photo requests, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Black Entertainment TV (BET), 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Black History Month, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Black History Museum and Culture Center, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Black History Museum and Culture Center, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Black Legislator's Caucus, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Black Virginia Pageant, Miss, Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Bonded debt, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Boys and Girls Club, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Boys State of Virginia (American Legion), 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Bridge Institute, Inc., 1986 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Brookings Institute, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Buchanan County (Va.), 1987 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Bunyan, Maureen, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Burriss, Roland W., 1987 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Busch Gardens, 1986-1988 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - C, 1986 January-June (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - C, 1986 July-September (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - C, 1986 October-December (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - C, 1987 January-May (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - C, 1987 June-November (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - C, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - C, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Capital Region Airport Commission, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Carrico, Harry L., 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Center for Innovative Technology, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Certificates, Presented to Lt. Governor Wilder, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Chesterfield County, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Children's letters, For speeches, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Central Intercollegiate Athletic Association, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Citizens to Commemorate the Virginia Statue for Religious Freedom, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Coca-Cola Mid-Atlantic Bottling, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Community Action Programs, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Community Learning Week, 1986-1988 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services and Training Council, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations, Eagle Scouts, 1987-1989 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations, General, A-G, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Coors, Adolph Co., 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Attorney General, 1986-1988 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Congressmen, 1986-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Delegates, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Delegates, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Delegates, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Creating Responsibility Through Early Student Training (CREST), 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Crime, 1987-1989 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Cumberland Hospital (New Kent, Va.), 1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - D, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - D, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - D, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - D, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Daily Planet, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Daniels Construction Co., 1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Day care, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Day care, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Delmarva trip, 1987 June (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Disabled American veterans, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Dulles Area Board of Trade, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - E, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - E, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - E, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Economic development, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Economic developments, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Election laws, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
    - Efficiency in Government, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhower Foundation, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Excellence in Education, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Export promotion- Virginia's approach, ca. 1985 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - F, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - F, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)